A Country Wedding is a romance, tv movie film directed by Anne Wheeler.
A famous country singer set to marry a glamorous Hollywood
actress returns to his small town roots.
When he crosses paths with his childhood sweetheart and finally feels inspired to write
songs again he reevaluates his life, his values and his opinion of true love.
As his wedding day approaches, he must decide if he has
chosen the right woman to be his wife.
Sarah Standor, played by Autumn Reeser.
Bradley Suttons, played by Jesse Metcalfe.
Catherine Mann, played by Laura Mennell.
Margaret Feldburg, played by Lauren Holly.
Adam, played by Aaron Craven.
James, played by Hrothgar Mathews.
A Country Wedding is a 2015 American-Canadian made-for-television romantic drama film directed
by Anne Wheeler and starring Jesse Metcalfe, Autumn Reeser, and Lauren Holly.
It premiered on Hallmark Channel on June 27, 2015.
The tone is emotional.